hey Brandon hey Tri
hey that's fitting to be y'all way
that's fitting to be y'all guys let me
tell you something do you know what the
view is going to be like up
there level one the realization of
what's going to happen hey Brandon
there's levels to this [__] level one oh
my God this is getting real my name is
Joe and my instructor's name also
conveniently Joe are we going to [__]
get it or not oh yeah oh yeah let's
going to get
it all right Brandon G's up here we go
they Tyler back there always in last
place level number two oh
boy we the last one out man yes sir he's
going first oh he is oh great Tyler
going first oh yes hey Brandon show me
what your face looks like when you found
that
out Tyler's going first that boy going
to [__] a brick hey Tyler you going
first big
dog look at him neck sweaty sweaty ass
neck hey bro cold on
the should one more gummy boy two more
Tyler when you see this later don't
don't be mad like this is hilarious we
know you're scared just admit
it there it is yes
sir yes sir level three the point of no
return turn back
now oh
boy only Ty level my get a little bit
swe
cuit very
Ru not break sh in your
rev you so ready for shoot your
yawning
s strap on get everything
ready hey Brandon you know why he
strapping up right go time baby
time time hey Tyler how you feeling
baby hey he
piss I cannot wait to see him on the
ground I cannot wait I love these guys
this is
great level
seven all right you can start to feel
this [__] now and they're leveling the
plane out oh boy hey the plane is
slowing down oh green light level
whatever the [__] we're at Tyler burges
I love you
boy yes sir come on Tyler take that [__]
like a bur Baby Go baby go yes sir sir
he's
down hey Brandon I love you dog hey
Brandon look at your M
Brandon all
right loaded let's go
yes
sir yes sir yes sir
yes sir I do not give me a moment yes
sir yes sir
hey show me how they do it up in PMW man
do you just go down like this or do you
do some
circles oh come on baby what the hell
that's what I come for oh baby
dude yes
sir yes
sir if I hit the ground and my nipples
AR hard you're not getting to chill
that's all I'm telling you Joe come on
Baby Woo yes
sir yes Dy
like yes sir I will talk [__] all day
long and you will do this look at the
mountain baby you got another one in you
yeah
okay get the [__] out of my way all
right well let's get some more
chees come on baby come on Baby G dump
oh yeah
hey yes sir Hey Joe let me ask you
something are you from USA hell yeah you
know how I knew that cuz everybody knows
gangsters are from the United States of
America hey that was a pretty good line
wasn't it you know who said that that's
a Nate Diaz line you know who that is oh
yeah Nate Diaz Army [__] y'all know you
could sell the second one for twice the
price of the
first get them hooked that's how we get
them
oh we are flying I am freeballing over
to PMW totally boxless the PMW D nuts
yes a little practice for the landing
okay for the landing all I need you to
do is lift those legs up perfect you're
going to feel something like this hey
bro sliding in on her butt dude I don't
know the way you phrased that was kind
of ambigous she said lift your legs up
you're going to feel something sliding
on you I'm strappy you
[__] dude this is
not got to be the most entertaining
T last bro you should you should [__]
party with me sometime he why do you
think I moved up here I'm 36 I'm
retired I can run 40 m without stopping
to swim 3 miles I'm [__] Fearless bro
I just want to hang out with people like
you if you want to do this [__] dial me
in I'll come Lear let me get certified
wouldn't you wouldn't you like to train
me to do this oh yeah yeah oh yeah you
teach me how to do this I'll teach you
how to eat mushrooms and run down the
towest time this sound like a good deal
all right going those legs
up well I thought we was going to drop
kick
somebody nice
W
yes we did it
baby
Char hey let me ask you what what do you
think about dirt biking now big dog huh
that was fun I ain't going Li [__] a
dirt bike my I like my dirt bikes now
hey dude that [__] like H Georgia I was
the first one out to playing y sry
[__] I was the very first one to
go [__] I said I said she said she said
CH your head back out and I let go
trying to get over to push myself over
she made me grab the thing right here
and she and she told me to pull my head
back and lean back I just put my legs in
front of
the gra my head and we [__]
went I was like
[Music]